http://www.altruwood.com/privacy-policy

Beams & Lumber
AltruWood – New Timbers.
Privacy Policy
By using the AltruWood, Inc. web site located at http://www.altruwood.com you are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy as outlined below. If you do not agree to these terms, do not use this site.
Collection of Personal Information
At times, particularly when you request publications or forms, download electronic files, or submit information through online forms from the AltruWood web site or via e-mail, we may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. It is completely optional for you to participate in these programs. If you elect to participate in these programs, however, we may require that you provide your contact information, which may include your name, mailing address, e-mail address, and other personal identifying information.
AltruWood collects this information in order to record and support your participation in the programs you select. If you register to receive notification of product specials, for example, the information may be used to register you with one of our electronic mailout databases so that we could include you in future mailings. AltruWood also uses information that you provide (through intentional disclosure through an online form, for example) as part of our effort to keep you informed about other services we may be able to provide. Other Internet Protocol (IP) information, as detailed below, may be collected so that we can better maintain statistics on our web site and in turn provide our users with better services and data, better ease of site navigation, and a more enjoyable web site experience overall.
AltruWood recognizes and appreciates the importance of responsible use of this information. If you do not want the information you provide to AltruWood to be used to inform you of other services from AltruWood, and you indicate this preference when you provide the information or request to AltruWood, AltruWood will honor your preference. AltruWood may share personal information in the form of a name, address, phone number, or email address with another agency for the sole purpose of answering an inquiry or forwarding an inquiry, but will not make the information publicly available in identifiable form, by any means including by a public posting, through the Internet, or through a home page of a website, a non-government electronic mail service, a message board, or a chat room. If you do not want the information you provide to AltruWood to be shared with other companies, and you indicate this preference when you provide the information to AltruWood, AltruWood will honor your preference.
Children’s Online Privacy Protection (COPPA)
AltruWood will not willingly or openly collect or distribute information or perform monetary transactions with children under the age of 13 in accordance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998. While this act is intended to apply to web sites and online services used for commercial purposes, in keeping with the intent and purpose of that protection act, AltruWood may share personal information in the form of a name, address, phone number, or email address with another agency for the sole purpose of answering the child’s inquiry or forwarding their inquiry, but will not make the information publicly available in identifiable form, by any means including by a public posting, through the Internet, or through a home page of a website, a pen pal service, a non-government electronic mail service, a message board, or a chat room.
Use of Cookies
When you visit our web site, you can surf the site anonymously and access important information without revealing your identity. In order to improve the AltruWood web site, we may use “cookies” to track your visit. A cookie is small amount of data that is transferred to your browser by a web server and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. It functions as your identification card, recording your passwords, purchases, and preferences. It cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses. Most browsers are set to accept cookies by default. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. (For some web pages that require an authorization, cookies are not optional. Users choosing not to accept cookies will probably not be able to access those pages.)
While AltruWood may use cookies to track your visit to the AltruWood web site (and our separate web servers), and our web servers may automatically log the IP address of your computer, this information does not identify you personally and you remain anonymous unless you have otherwise provided AltruWood with personal information.
FSC Certified Wood Products
View Products
Reclaimed Lumber
View Products
Decking
Ipe Flooring
Cedar Decking Flooring
Beams & Lumber
Sitemap
Copyright © 2003-2018 Altruwood.
All Rights Reserved.
The FSC tick-mark tree logo, the FSC initials, and the FSC name "Forest Stewardship Council" are registered trademarks of Forest Stewardship Council®, A.C. in the United States and other countries.
Altruwood | 5125 SW Macadam Ave Ste #135, Portland, Oregon 97239 | 1-877-407-9788
